in this tutorial I'll be demonstrating
在本教程中，我将演示
how you can use inkscape to trace an
如何使用Inkscape跟踪
image into a series of individual Vector
将图像转化为一系列单独的矢量
color dots and to show you what I mean
彩色点，并向你展示我的意思
for my example here I started off with
在我的示例中，我从
this image which is a pixel-based image
该图像是基于像素的图像
and I was able to trace a series of
我能够追踪到一系列
vector dots that all have a single fill
全部具有单一填充的矢量点
color and no gradients applied which is
颜色，且未应用渐变，
what I'll be showing in this tutorial
我将在本教程中展示的内容
before we get started though if you'd
在我们开始之前，如果你愿意
like to learn more about inkscape be
想了解更多关于Inkscape BE的信息
sure to check out my inkscape master
一定要看看我的Inkscape大师
class it's a collection of over 60
班级它是一个超过60个人的集合
videos where I go over all of the tools
我浏览了所有工具的视频
and features in inkscape and I explain
和Inkscape中的功能，我解释
what they are and demonstrate how they
它们是什么并演示它们如何
work we even have a private Community
工作我们甚至有一个私人社区
where you can ask questions and get help
在这里您可以提出问题并获得帮助
from me any time you want I'll have some
任何时候你想要我的，我都会有
information about that down below if you
下面是关于这方面的信息，如果你
want to check that out so to get started
我想检查一下，这样就开始了
I'm going to import my image into
我要把我的形象导入到
inkscape and I want to make sure I have
Inkscape和我想确保我有
my document the same size as the image
我的文档与图像大小相同
so click on the image and press control
所以点击图像并按下Ctrl键
shift R if you haven't done so already
Shift R(如果您还没有这样做)
and that will make the document the same
这将使文档保持相同
size as the selected image now let's
所选图像的大小现在让我们
open up the layers menu by going to
通过转到打开层菜单
layer and selecting layers and objects
层和选择层和对象
and I want to make sure I have my image
我想确保我有我的形象
on one layer by itself and I'm going to
只有一层，我要
add another layer on top of that so I'll
在上面再加一层，这样我就
click on this plus icon up here and I'm
点击这里的加号图标，我就是
going to name this layer to which is the
要将此层命名为
default and I'll click
默认，然后我将单击
add and on this layer I want to create a
在这个层上，我想创建一个
circle so I'm going to zoom into the top
圆圈，所以我要放大到顶部
left corner of my image and I'm going to
我的图像的左角，我要
grab the circles and ellipses tool and
抓起圆形和椭圆工具并
I'll click and drag to draw a circle and
我会点击并拖动来画一个圆圈
I'll hold the control key while doing so
这样做的时候，我会按住控制键
to make sure I can draw a perfectly
为了确保我能完美地画出
round circle like that so now I'll grabb
像这样圆的圆圈，所以现在我要抓住
my selection tool and I'll open up the
我的选择工具和我将打开
fill and stroke menu by going to object
通过转到对象来选择填充和描边菜单
and selecting fill and
并选择填充和
stroke and I'll come over here to the
斯帕克，我会到这里来
fill Tab and I want to make sure I
填充制表符，我想确保我
choose this option right here which says
请在此处选择此选项，它会显示
unset paint and when you have an unset
取消设置绘画和当您有一个取消设置
paint it should turn black by default
默认情况下，应将其涂成黑色
and what that will do is it'll make it
它所做的就是它会成功
so that this object can trace all of the
以便此对象可以跟踪所有
objects it can trace the objects beneath
它可以跟踪下面的对象的对象
it and Sample a color from each copy
并从每个副本中采样一种颜色
that we create so let me take this and
我们创造的，所以让我拿着这个
put this in the top left corner I'm
把这个放在左上角我是
going to open up the aligned distribute
要打开对齐的分布
menu by going to object and selecting
菜单，方法是转到对象并选择
aligned
对齐
distribute I'll set the relative two
分配，我会设置相对的两个
make sure you have this set to page and
确保您已将此设置为PAGE并
I'm going to align this on the top Edge
我要将此对齐到顶部边缘
and the left Edge and I'm going to zoom
左边缘和我要放大
out a little bit just as a
就像是一个
comparison I'm going to make the
我要做的比较是
circle about that big you can eyeball it
绕着那个大点转一圈，你就能看到它
doesn't have to be a specific size I'll
不一定要有特定的尺码，我会
go with that size right there and what
就穿那个尺码吧，怎么样？
you want to do now is click on your
您现在要做的是单击您的
image and look up here in the width and
图像，然后抬头看这里的宽度和
the height to see what the width and
要看的高度是什么，宽度和
height is and make a mental note of
身高是并在脑海中记录下来的
whatever that is so my image is 872 by
不管它是什么，所以我的图像是872乘以
1280 so I'll select my circle now and
所以我现在要选择我的圆圈
with the circle selected I will go to
选中圆圈后，我将转到
edit clone create tiled
编辑克隆创建切片
clones and from this menu I want to
克隆和从这个菜单中我想要
choose this option over here that says
选择这里的选项，上面写着
width and height and I want to input the
宽度和高度，我想输入
width and height of my image so I'm
我的图像的宽度和高度，所以我
going to write 872 by 1280
到1280年将写出872
and then I'll come over here to the
然后我会到这里来
trace tab I want to enable tracing and I
跟踪选项卡我要启用跟踪，并且我
want to enable color and I want to turn
我想启用颜色，并且我想要打开
off everything else so whatever else in
所有其他的东西，所以不管里面还有什么
here is enabled turn that off we only
此处已启用关闭，仅限我们
want Trace color and color and width and
想要痕迹颜色和颜色和宽度
height and once that's done let me make
身高，一旦做完了，让我做
sure I have my object selected first
当然，我首先选择了我的对象
there we go my object got deselected
开始了，我的对象被取消选择
somehow that's important you got to have
不知何故，这很重要，你必须拥有
your object selected and now I will make
您的对象已选定，现在我将创建
sure I have everything set here and then
当然，我已经把一切都准备好了。
click create and when you click create
单击创建，然后单击创建
it may take a minute or two to load
它可能需要一两分钟才能加载
because it's pretty CPU intensive mine
因为我的电脑是CPU密集型的
rendered pretty quick though so as you
渲染得很快，就像你
can see the tracing has completed I'm
可以看到追踪已经完成了我是
going to click the x button to get out
点击x按钮就可以出去了
of this menu and if you zoom in on this
如果你放大这个菜单
a little bit you can see the individual
一点点，你可以看到个人
color dots that were traced over the
追踪到的彩色点
image and what you could do now is you
你现在可以做的就是你自己
can scale them down if you want so if I
如果你想的话我可以把它们缩小如果我
were to select this dot if I were to
如果我选择了这个点
hold my ALT key or if you're on Mac it
按住我的Alt键，或者如果你在使用Mac It
would be the option key and click again
将是选项键，然后再次单击
I would select the original dot on
我会选择原始点上的
underneath it and I would scale that
在它的下面，我会把它
down by holding control and shift and
通过按住Ctrl和Shift并按下
then scaling that down just a little bit
然后再稍微缩小一点
and the rest of the dots scale down with
其余的点按比例缩小
it now I'm going to turn off the
现在我要关掉
visibility of the background image so
背景图像的可见性
you can see this even better I'll come
你可以看得更清楚，我会去的
over here to my layers menu and I'll
在这里到我的层菜单，我会
come all the way down here to the bottom
一路走到这里，一直到底部
of the layers menu and I'm going to turn
在层菜单中，我要将
off the visibility of layer one and you
从第一层的可见性和您的
can now see if you zoom out you can see
现在可以看到，如果您缩小，您可以看到
the image better but what I'm going to
图像更好，但我要做的是
do now is put a background Behind these
Do Now是把背景放在这些背后
dots so you can see it better so I'll
点，这样你就能看得更清楚，所以我会
grab my rectangle
抓住我的矩形
tool I'll send this to the bottom and
工具，我会把这个送到底部
now you can see it a little better okay
现在你可以看得更清楚一点，好吗？
so if I zoom in you can see each dot
所以如果我放大，你可以看到每个点
here is individually colored I could
这是单独的颜色，我可以
select on each one and you can see the
选择每个选项，您可以看到
color that's applied there there's no
涂在那里的颜色，没有
gradients here each dot is a single
渐变这里的每个点都是一个单独的
individual
个人
color and that should do it for this
颜色，这样就可以了。
tutorial that's how you can trace an
教程，这就是如何跟踪
image into a series of vector colored
将图像转化为一系列有色的矢量
dots using inkscape
使用Inkscape的点
if you found this lesson useful then
如果你觉得这一课很有用，那么
consider checking out my inkscape master
考虑一下我的Inkscape大师
class it's a collection of over 60
班级它是一个超过60个人的集合
videos where I go over all of the tools
我回顾所有工具的视频
and features in inkscape and I explain
墨水景观中的特征和我解释
what they are and demonstrate how they
它们是什么并展示它们如何
work kind of like how I did in this
工作有点像我在这件事上的表现
video we even have a private Community
视频我们甚至有一个私人社区
where you can ask questions and get help
您可以在那里提出问题并获得帮助
from me anytime you want and best of all
随时从我这里收到，最好的是
there's no monthly membership fees you
没有每月会员费
just pay $17 one time and you're in for
只需一次支付17美元，您就能获得
Life I'll have some information about
生活我会有一些信息
that down below if you want to check
如果你想检查的话，请在下面
that out as always thanks for watching
一如既往地感谢收看
oh
哦
[Music]
[音乐]